[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1",
    "question": "A trinomial has ___ terms",
    "options": [
      " 2",
      " 3",
      " 1",
      " 4"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2",
    "question": "The degree of the polynomial<br> 3x<sup>3</sup> - 5x<sup>2</sup>y + 2x<sup>2</sup>yz<sup>2</sup> is ____",
    "options": [
      " 3",
      " 2",
      " 4",
      " 5"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3",
    "question": "Which of the following algebraic expressions is not a polynomial.",
    "options": [
      " x²y + 2x²y",
      " 3x² + 2x - 3/5",
      " 5x² - 4x + 1/z",
      " xyz"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4",
    "question": "Write in algebraic language: Twice the sum of the square of x and half of the cube of y.",
    "options": [
      " 2x<sup>2</sup> + y<sup>3</sup>/2",
      " x<sup>2</sup> + y<sup>3</sup>",
      " x<sup>2</sup> - y<sup>3</sup>",
      " 2x<sup>2</sup> - y<sup>3</sup>"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5",
    "question": "The coefficient of xy in 2x<sup>2</sup>y is ______",
    "options": [
      " 2xy",
      " xy",
      " 2x",
      " 2y"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6",
    "question": "The number of terms in the expression<br> 7x² - 2xy - 5z + 9 is _______",
    "options": [
      " 1",
      " 2",
      " 3",
      " 4"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7",
    "question": "The like term of 3x<sup>2</sup>y is______",
    "options": [
      " 3x<sup>2</sup>y<sup>2</sup>",
      " 3xy<sup>2</sup>",
      " 3xy",
      " 9x<sup>2</sup>y"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8",
    "question": "Which of the following is a monomial",
    "options": [
      " 3",
      " 9xyz",
      " 5xy<sup>2</sup>",
      " All the above"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9",
    "question": "Which of the following is a binomial",
    "options": [
      " 2x - 3y",
      " (2x)(3y)",
      " (2x)/(3y)",
      " All of the above"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10",
    "question": "Add 2x + 3y and 3y²",
    "options": [
      " 2x + 3y<sup>2</sup>",
      " 2x + 6y<sup>2</sup>",
      " 2x + 6y<sup>3</sup>",
      " 2x + 3y + 3y<sup>2</sup>"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q11",
    "question": "Which of the following is a trinomial",
    "options": [
      " 5x<sup>3</sup>/y<sup>2</sup>- 3y + 3y<sup>2</sup>",
      " (5x<sup>3</sup>)(z<sup>4</sup>) - 3y + 3y<sup>2</sup>/∛z<sup>4</sup>",
      " x + z - 9",
      " All of the above"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q12",
    "question": "Subtract 5x² - 7x + 5 from x² + 3x + 5",
    "options": [
      " 4x² + 10x + 5",
      " 4x² + 10x",
      " 4x² - 4x + 5",
      " -1x² + 10x + 0"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q13",
    "question": "The degree of 29 is",
    "options": [
      " 0",
      " 1",
      " 2",
      " does not exist"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q14",
    "question": "Is 127 a polynomial?",
    "options": [
      " yes",
      " no"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q15",
    "question": "Add 2x² - 2x + 5 and -2x² - 6 - 6x",
    "options": [
      " -4x² + 4x - 1",
      " 4x² + 4x - 1",
      " -8x - 1",
      " 4x² - 4x + 1"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  }
]
